<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex Does Stuff (and Things)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Alex Does Stuff (and Things)]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 07:10:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Video shootin'!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Video shootin'!</h1><p>So today I actually did some shooting for a promotional video I helped write and edit for my friend's latest game prototype. This was interesting, since it was the first time ever that I have shot video. I have a raw blooper clip of me forgetting a line that I'd like to upload here, but I'll settle for linking to it (click here) instead. As for Grid matters, more UI updates. The "add media" button in drafts is now an icon of a landscape (photo frame, mountains). No other concrete updates that I can see. I tweaked my design guidelines again, and plan to publish them when I publish this post. I'll probably edit this text again if I wind up not liking it and reverting to my previous setup. 'Til next time, folks!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cad9ab699320e093b13b961539f98a2a73189c19.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/video-shootin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">497b3a0d-13b9-4460-9788-f98d1bf584cb</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 07:09:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updates 'n' things!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Updates 'n' things!</h1><p>Alright, take 2 on today's update post. The content guidelines are still the same, as are the options available for each of these posts while they are in draft form (minimal formatting/title/description options). I like how the guidelines allow you to review the changes before publishing them, but that particular UI is a bit garish (solid, bright yellow background). There is a new method for adding images, however. Besides the content-adding Plus sign on the left side of each new line break, there is a specific "Add Image" button that I will be testing with this update. That image will be a recent shot taken from Fort Lee Historic Park, across the Hudson River towards Manhattan. Part of a small shoot you can see in full by clicking here.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/205812e424dcdcc767ac186794d7a9a4150d18e9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/updates-n-things/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a897b06e-73c1-44d5-8d14-f45bfad94e4f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 01:47:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NYC Night Lights]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>NYC Night Lights</h1><p>After a lengthy absence, I return to see The Grid's made still more updates/upgrades to the UI. I like what I see. Unfortunately, I'm making this update very quickly while I remember to do so, in between other errands. I'll try to remember to make another post later tonight, which will take a closer look at the updates (and provide another image). This shot is from 5th Ave. in Manhattan. F/18, 20sec. exposure, ISO 100. Click here for the (very small) album.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/72e75ca3820228b8501222a1c22264e3f6cff30a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/5a317246-2240-4dfb-bf9f-2fd6a3780824/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a317246-2240-4dfb-bf9f-2fd6a3780824</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 22:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[YouTube Share Test - Fire Tornado from The Slow Mo Guys]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>YouTube Share Test - Fire Tornado from The Slow Mo Guys</h1><p>So it turns out that Grid does video shares by making the title clickable, not the image. I wonder if we'll get an Embed option in the future. Could be cool to actually be able to throw the video here so it's playable! </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f61e4f376c059abae10b22153ac9dc9d560611b4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QwoghxwETng</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b71bb922-f344-4219-a58b-76f62bda8228</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 07:19:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Day... four?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Day... four?</h1><p>I skipped a day. I had planned to try something new each day and make a mini-post here. Woops. That'll happen when Battlefront launches and you've been playing Fallout 4 way too much.

The other day, I tried a Navigation/Page post, but I couldn't get the image to work the way I wanted. Same thing as the other day: I was trying to get the text to overlay on the image, but the UI wasn't cooperating. So, as of right now, you can click through the nav at the top to a text-only page with some of my social media accounts.

I'm hoping that, eventually, one is able to add new posts to existing pages. The plan is to create separate pages for a "doin' stuff" blog (gaming, travel, things to do around town) and a photo portfolio. But right now, I don't think I can tell a new draft to, say, add itself to my Social Media page.

Also, Click here for the link to the album for today's photo.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/af9ea0611a9776c0d2a255b51cbba56f78a0dc51.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alex-does-stuff-and-things/day-four/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e517ce63-3970-4c6e-b3aa-cd4723a6c7ee</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 23:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>